Contact

jaynaropasingh@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jaynsingh (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Diversified executive leadership & acute care experience.

Master of Science GPA 3.9 from Molloy College

Administrative of SNF that includes ventilator care (90 beds).

Jay Narain-Singh MSN, NE-BC, CMSRN

Sigma Theta Tau

Greater New York City Area

Summary

Accomplished nursing professional with 20 years of diversified executive level and clinical experience.

Masters prepared GPA 3.9: board certified Nurse Executive and certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse.

Achieve fiscal viability via diligent budgetary monitoring and promotion of cost containment initiatives.

Broad experience in human resource recruitment, retention, training and overall program development.

Strong interpersonal skills with demonstrated ability to cultivate multidisciplinary and community relationships.

Decision making that reflects sound analytical ability with dedication to obtaining and sustaining service excellence.

Experience

Margaret Tietz Nursing and Rehabilitation Center Director Of Nursing January 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months)

The Silvercrest Center
Asst DON- Associate Director - Vice President Of Nursing
July 2008 - December 2017 (9 years 6 months)
United States

NewYork-Presbyterian Hospital Nurse Manager-Administrative Nursing Supervisor May 2001 - June 2008 (7 years 2 months) United States

Education

Molloy College

BSN & MSN , Bachelor's & Masters in Nursing: Sigma Theta Tau